PhimLe.TV
Xin giới thiệu phim
Orange Marmalade - Ma Cà Rồng Biết Yêu
Tập 2
♫ Even if you're lonely, do not express it ♫
♫ Accept and live the way they are ♫
♫ Don't get discourged ♫
If a kid like that is our band's vocal...
♫ Hold it in even if tears fall ♫
♫ Now stop being ♫
Then you can do that.
♫ the first one ♫
Huh?
♫ to get ♫
That kid...
♫ wounded ♫
is from our school.
♫ Do not try ♫
♫ so hard ♫
Our class' transfer student.
♫ Don't force yourself ♫
Episode 2
For the first time in history of our TV station,
we attempted an interview with a vampire.
Living in our society
we were able to listen to a very shocking story.
Viewers, please listen to this interview to the end.
Living in our society
but, there identities are not exactly revealed
Vampire interview?
... it will be revealed for the very first time.
Is this Han Shi Hoo?
Han Shi Hoo.
I suppose that is my new name this time?
That's right.
Vampire clan's media and interviews and all
activities that may cause a havoc socially are managed by us
Punishments for under age activities were decided
but, just in case documents for new name and ID are prepared.
I am not going to school anymore.
VCS is notifying your new name Han ShiWoo and transfer school
I am done with school
Until VCS' decision has been implemented, your SPA will be discontinued.
Where's that kind of thing?!
We invite you to participate.
Humans are so cool.
one day, your next door neighbor is a vampire.
If you find out, what are you going to do?
Every time that happens, vampires have to run away.
Look at what we are.
Do you see this?
This is bad news.
Vampires are superior to humans.
We gave up our abilities.
What do humans mean when they say "coexist"?
What's wrong with me?
Why do I keep thinking about a person's blood?
I think I'm becoming
more and more of a monster.
Ah!
I heard you were almost a legend. That you were the best in your middle school band.
Did you practice that in just one day?
- Yeah.
- Wow~
My son is so great.
What about you?
Mom...
I'm happiest when I hear my Jae Min playing the guitar.
Can you play for me one more time?
Okay.
If that kind of girl is our band's vocal...
What to do?
Why is he like that?
Look
See what we really are.
- I don't like this sound.
- This is no joke. Ahh!
Oh my gosh! Wow!
- Ah!
- Why?
This is really no joke.
Vampires are superior to humans.
We gave up our abilities.
What's wrong?
Why can't I replay it?
- It's not broken...
Why!
Something about a girl?
Who is it? Is she pretty? Is she?
THE BAND Practice Room
Hey! Hyung, is she pretty? Why won't you answer?
- Is she pretty!?
- It's none of my business.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Nice catch.
You said you don't know how to play the guitar.
What is it?
You... Did you remember? What you need to apologize for?
Give it.
Thankfully it seems you remember me now.
But in turn, did you say you would run away if you saw me?
I said to give it.
I'm...
like dust. Do you want to blow me away?
What?
You haven't answered any of my questions.
This is outright treating a person like dust--
It's not like that.
Do you want to join a band?
I hear they're making a school band.
You like music and you're good at it.
If you do it,
I'm thinking of doing it, too.
I'm not doing that kind of thing.
What did I ever do?
Why does she always run away when she sees me?
Baek Ma Ri. Do you know you're really strange?
♫ You, who disappears when I try to touch you ♫
♫ You ♫
♫ I'm afraid of you, you made me like this, ♫
♫ I want to erase it ♫
♫ I'm afraid of you, ♫
Don't you want to join the band club?
I hear they're forming a school band.
Band club... sounds fun.
I'm doing it. Just once.
Yeah, this school break try the literature program.
Just once.
In turn, I have a condition.
I have a voice I want to match with my guitar.
Baek Ma Ri.
Vampire Control System
Yes?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Are you okay?
Why is your body so cold?
You haven't eaten yet.
Wounds that come from the light don't heal well.
Unless you follow the instructions given from the VCS (Vampire Control System),
living as a vampire in this society is difficult.
Stop teaching. Why do you always try to teach?
SPA
(Sun Protection Ample)
You're going to go to school,
Shi Woo.
SPA
(Sun Protection Ample)
How about breakfast?
I'm late!
That's why I told you to wake up five minutes earlier!
I'll be back!
- I'll be back!
- Yes...
Honey!
- Why?
- This!
Ma Ri!
- Dad!
- Ma Ri, Ma Ri!
Ah, your lunch.
Ah, sorry, Dad.
My daughter... something troubling you lately?
Yesterday, you didn't eat dinner, and today at breakfast too..
It's nothing.
You'll be in big trouble if you don't drink blood in over 12 hours.
Just think about it as the first and second halves of the day and
eat even if you don't feel like it.
You're going to be late. Hurry and go.
You should go back, Dad.
Okay. Go now.
Getting the instruments was the hardest challenge for us.
Tell your father that I said thank you.
Just tell him some nice words, please.
Yes, Teacher.
But Ah Ra...
Yes?
Are you by chance friends with Baek Ma Ri?
Ah, the new kid who transferred?
Yeah. If you're friends with her, can you persuade her to join?
I would like it if Baek Ma Ri were vocals in our band.
Jae Min, that rascal, said that he would join band on the condition that Ma Ri was vocals,
so if you're close with Ma Ri, please try to persuade her.
Ma Ri!
Help, help. Let's go quickly.
Be careful, careful, so it doesn't break.
Okay now. The competition place is in a 10 minute distance,
so we're going to arrive before lunch ends.
Get on!
Teacher!
- I...
- What are you doing? Get on, quickly!
He said that he has to bring these over quickly.
You guys worked hard.
Should we go and eat? How about pizza?
- We like it!
- Pizza, pizza, pizza...
Pizza, pizza, pizza!
Pizza, pizza!
- Teacher...
Can't I get off from here and go to school?
What?
Why? Are you hurt somewhere?
- Ah, so irritating.
Let's go home. Hurry, hurry. I have to go home.
If I don't have blood...
What's wrong?
Baek Ma Ri.
This is... the scent of blood?
It's sweet.
synced by riri13
Blood... I can't hold it in now.
I want to bite and eat it!
No!
Are you okay?
Go away.
What is he doing?
Hey! Where's the nurse room?
There, there.
That's daebak!
Hey! You'll get indigestion. Drink slowly.
If you get indigestion from drinking blood, there's no medicine for that.
- I didn't eat, starting from yesterday night.
- Why?
We can't do things like dieting.
- Taking blood regularly every 12 hours is basic vampire knowl-
- Hey!
Nobody is here. The school nurse said she will go eat lunch, and I closed the door right away.
Be careful.
You... What would you have done if I wasn't there?
You're thankful, right?
- Aren't you thankful that I recognized you right away, too?
- Yeah.
But how did you know it was me?
We've shared blood before so it's a given.
We were in a relationship where we even shared blood from the same bowl.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
I recognized her right at first glance. Transferring,
isn't so bad, now that I'm here, thanks to her.
Your locker doesn't open?
So you couldn't change into your gym clothes because your locker wouldn't open.
That's pretty fresh for an excuse, but it smells.
It smells like a lie.
How shall we pass go about PE?
Um, Teacher! I don't think Ma Ri would have a reason to lie.
So that's why we should check. Vice president, you go and check.
- What's your password?
- 4-0-3
- Go!
- Yes.
Baek Ma Ri, the consequence of a lie are laps.
I'll give you time to meditate about honesty on the school grounds.
Change and run!
Hurry!
- How many laps do you have left?
- Two laps.
- Aren't you going to class?
- It ended.
But you're good at acting. You seem like a real human.
Be quiet!
- I'm giving my full effort to be normal.
- Normal?
You're so senseless.
Hey, people are thinking that you're abnormal.
- About what?
- I think you've been picked (to be the outcast) by the kids.
That means it's hopeless to be normal.
Why do you think they pulled the locker prank?
You received a punishment because of something you didn't do,
And you're lying by acting as if you're being properly punished.
You're pretty cool.
If Coach knew, he would go crazy.
The fact that Baek Ma Ri is a vampire who wouldn't even be fazed by running around the schoolyard a hundred times.
You!
I heard that the new transfer student carried Baek Ma Ri and took her to the school infirmary.
They said he was a black night (a man who solves difficult situation for a woman).
Han Shi Woo... doesn't his pose look like a model?
Bling bling!
Look at how long his legs are!
Go away. Because of you, all the kids are looking.
Jerks. Just because they can see.
I don't like being noticed. Go to the classroom quickly.
- Look at your sweat!
Why are they like that? Are the transfer students openly having a "some" relationship?
Ma Ri fainted and went to the infirmary during lunch.
Do you think she's okay?
- Look at her playing.
- She's perfectly fine.
- It was all an act.
Anyways, it's sure that she's a liar.
You better faint again as we run. More naturally.
I told you to go.
You're so prepared. Even thinking about sweat.
Since it's gym.
- Give me some too.
We're running together, and it's weird that I'm not sweating, either.
Just say you're the type that doesn't sweat.
Is he flirting on his first day?
He is good looking, he has everything.
What are you doing?
- Stay still.
Is it done? Are you the only one sweating? I'm sweating too.
W-What's wrong?
Don't even try hitting on my Ah Ra.
Let's go together!
Ah Ra, are you okay?
What's wrong?
- I was a bit surprised.
- Ah, that scared me! I thought it was blood!
Tomato juice?
What in the world?
Who is it? Who did this?
Baek Ma Ri, can you open your locker?
The locker that you couldn't open, but Ah Ra could?
That's an interesting locker.
Why my locker?
I saw you drinking tomato juice yesterday.
You must really like tomato juice.
What does that have anything to do with you?
It doesn't, but this is...
I don't think this is a coincidence.
What do you mean?
What it means is, if there's tomato juice coming out of your locker, by chance,
I'll tell you if these are similar or not, after I compare it.
No wonder. My presentment...
Don't talk nonsense. How could you without evidence -
That's why we should find out if there is any evidence now.
I think so too.
In our class, there's no one who would do this to Ah Ra.
Hey, honestly, you're annoyed, right?
Since your locker opened, and since Ah Ra took out your gym clothes,
were you that annoyed to give her a punishment like that?!
Stop it, Ae Kyung.
Now that I think about it, my thinking was short.
I should've just told the PE teacher that it wouldn't open.
Ah Ra, why you?
Just because she lied.
- I didn't lie!
So, let's open your locker!
I saw you take out your gym clothes earlier.
Is it not opening now? Let's open it!
Don't be like this!
I told you to open it!
Ah! Don't do this!
Move! You're not moving?
Get out of the way!
Don't do it!
- I told you to get out of the way!
Aish!
I told you to get out of the way!
Hey, don't be like this!
What are you doing, in the classroom?
What do you think this act is, in the classroom?
You...
Why are you treating her like this?
Open the locker? With what rights?
Are you going to inspect her belongings?
If she did nothing wrong, she can just open her locker!
Just because Ma Ri has tomato juice,
doesn't mean that she did this. Does that even make sense?
- You guys, let's not-
- Today
other than meal time and PE, everyone was in the classroom.
Baek Ma Ri was in the infirmary at lunch,
and since she was receiving a punishment at gym, she came the latest.
- Just when, with what time, did she-
- Hey, Jung Jae Min
What's with the Sherlock act? Are you some sort of detective?
Anyways, it's not Baek Ma Ri.
Then, who is there in the classroom who would do this to Baek Ma Ri?
Here.
I like tomato juice too.
What is it?
- It's tomato juice.
I also have grape juice.
Really!
What?
Sorry.
But you
are pretty when you're shocked.
So cool!
Daebak!
Han Shi Hoo!
Did you really do this?
Why?
I have interest in you.
Oh!
Let's drink tomato juice together next time.
I'll buy.
Hey, hey, hey!
That bastard! You heard him right?
Hey, we heard him right, right?
Hey, hey, come here!
Okay, okay. We got it.
That bastard!
- We know. We really heard him.
Okay. Let's go on.
♫ There's this person. ♫
♫ Someone who wants to be normal. ♫
♫ There's a person. ♫
♫ On a day that seems like any other ♫
I couldn't find another person to go with. I must have no popularity.
Want to go together?
♫ There's this person. ♫
♫ On a day that seems like any other ♫
Let's go.
♫ You probably don't have interest, ♫
♫ That sort of love is more prominent than you think ♫
Aren't you going home?
♫ Quietly, alone ♫
You're spacing out on the street.
Jae Min, when I got these tickets, I thought I would see it with you from the start.
♫ A long ago story. ♫
But, is this guitarist that famous?
♫ I'm just living. ♫
Jae Min.
♫ You probably have no interest in me, ♫
Yeah?
- Let's go. ♫ That kind of person, ♫
Thanks.
♫ is more than I thought. ♫
♫ Like I don't and do have it, quietly, ♫
♫ I spend my day alone. ♫
You're not sitting?
I'm okay.
Are you perhaps close to him?
Jung Jae Min.
No.
That person's name was Jung Jae Min, too.
Be happy, uncle.
Thanks for the congratulating me.
Jung Jae Min
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Should I tell you a scary secret?
My mom married a vampire today.
Jae Min, you're joining band, right?
Let's do it! My dad said he'd get us the best instruments.
It has been a while since I've played.
My hands are probably all stiff.
Aigoo, Jae Min.
When we're 12th graders, we can only study.
Then, we won't have any high school memories.
Is that so?
Of course. If you don't do high school band now, you can't do it later.
Think about it.
If not now, you can't do it. If the chance passes you, you can't do it. Forever.
Yeah. That's so...
forever. You're right.
If I don't do it now, I can't do it ever again.
Right?
If it's not now,
I can't do it. If it's not now.
Ah Ra, I'm really sorry,
but I can't go to the performance today. There's an emergency.
What?
Driver, drop me off here.
♫ At the street corner where the seasons pass by ♫
Ah Ra, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Jae Min!
Taxi!
♫ The times I want to share with you, ♫
♫ are standing absent-mindedly. ♫
♫ Don't hold on to me. ♫
Stop following me. Let's see each other at school tomorrow.
I'm not following you, but you're going the way I'm going.
Some misinterpretation.
Is your house really this way? Really?
My mouth hurts.
(from answering so many times)
You lived in this neighborhood too? Since when?
♫ Again, love, ♫
♫ Saying there is no farewell ♫
Baek Ma Ri... You...
said you don't remember
why you had to apologize?
Should I...
make you remember?
♫ I try to swallow my tears ♫
♫ and crying again ♫.
♫ I can't keep you out. I can't have you either. ♫
♫ The day I can't do anything ♫
♫ A finished, ♫
Orange Marmalade
♫ love ♫
A smart guys like you is no good.
Can you like someone you can't understand like Baek Ma Ri?
[Orange Marmalade]
Because of you, I'm picking up the guitar for the first time in 4 years.
I didn't play on purpose, trying to fight it.
At first I was scared.
Every time I saw him, I couldn't resist the desire to taste the sweet scent.
Sorry that I like you.
If it's like that, keep on being sorry.
For as long as you want.
♫ But I can't see you.
I can't find you either. ♫