PhimLe.TV
Xin giới thiệu phim
Orange Marmalade - Ma Cà Rồng Biết Yêu
Tập 1
Let's go together. Let's go together.
I want to go with you, too.
Don't do it.
I don't like it.
Don't go
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not a monster.
- Go! Leave!
- Get out of here!
I'm not. I'm not a monster.
Stop it!
I mean... What are you all looking at?
Student, what's wrong?
I'm the only one who's becoming the strange one!
Did I do anything to you?
You did it to me! Me!
What's wrong with this woman?
This person is a rapist.
That guy is a rapist. Did you get that?
What are they saying?
Where are you going?!
Ah, why are you being like this? Seriously!
What's with you...
Get that guy!
You... go to my school, right?
I smell blood.
Are you okay?
Blood! It's sweet blood.
I asked if you were okay. Can you stand by yourself?
This blood...
I want to eat it.
This is Seomu Station.
Your exit is to the right.
If you plan to go in the direction of the bus terminal
please get off at this station.
Hey!
What's with her?
If you get off, you're going to be late for school.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Why... am I attracted to a human's blood?
Come to your senses, Baek Ma Ri.
You're... not a monster.
Episode 1
I will definitely... graduate from this school.
Baek Ma Ri
I will no longer be chased.
This time, it will absolutely not be discovered,
that I'm a vampire.
Now, Jung Jae Min, come up and solve it.
Yes.
Yes?
- She's the new transfer student.
- Ah, yes.
Now, new transfer student? Baek Ma Ri. Right, well...
Being tardy on the first day has the most impact, right?
You can introduce yourself later. For now, go sit at that empty desk over there.
What are you doing? Are you not going to solve it?
Yes?
Solve it.
- Ah, yes.
See? I told you you'd be late.
Ma Ri? I'm Soo Ri. Welcome, welcome! You have more guts than you look.
The class is almost over.
Yeah...
It's a vampire!
- Awesome!
Hey, look at this. You...
This is our school uniform!
- Oh? You're right.
It's true!
- Wait...
Isn't that her? The transfer student?
- You're right. - I think you're right.
Is... this really you?
Woah, awesome, awesome! Guys! It is Ma Ri! It really is her!
Awesome! Wow!
- Hey! Hey!-- It's really her!
Really?
- Then, you were sitting right next to a vampire?
Yeah.
Wow, seriously awesome.
- Were the vampire's
teeth really sharp? And his eyes red?
Hey! Is he a rabbit, for his eyes to be red?
He looks exactly like a human at first glance!
If his eyes are red, then how can he ride the subway?
Don't look at me like that.
Just wondering... didn't he feel cold?
Like a zombie corpse?
Zombies are in the movies but vampires are right now.
Stop it.
A vampire touching me?
Stop it, please.
That vampire... didn't do anything to you?
I heard you sat next to him.
You must've been so scared.
It's probably because of this.
What is that?
Vampires are scared of crosses.
Ah, right, right.
I hate this... these kinds of lies.
Relax, just say you experienced a fright.
It's not like you'd run into another vampire again, right?
But... I'm a... vampire
Their beginning is not recorded.
They've been by our side for a long time,
[Between the living and the dead]
surviving through human blood.
Not a person, but something that appeared like a person. A ghost.
Like this, they were rumored to exist in past generations
and were revealed as reality in the 17th century.
Killings were done secretly for generations and
just before extinction, Joseon Royalty and the vampire clans
made a peace treaty.
It would have been better if they had gone extinct.
Those vampires.
Excuse me, Teacher.
How can we believe you? That peace treaty.
Where is the guarantee that we will be protected?
Because of the strict system that was maintained,
and as you all know the main focus on the peace treaty
was to not consume human blood. In return,
the vampires lives were protected.
Humans and vampires found a way to coexist.
Coexistence?
Show me. Go and you will know.
Why? In our society, coexistence exists. Humans and vampires, together.
Mr. PD (Producing Director).
Someday, if your neighbor was a vampire,
and you came to know, what would you do?
It's dangerous! You said they consume alternative blood,
but it's still blood nonetheless...
It's scary! Let's assume, what if some vampire suddenly turned back and sucked someone's blood?
It would be scary. It would be uneasy.
We would have to alert the authorities
that a vampire lives next door,
and every time the vampires would run away.
This is, from the point of view of humans, coexistence, isn't it?
Do you even understand what the meaning of coexistence is?
Why do we have to coexist?
There are only a few of them anyway.
Can't we just get rid of them?
Vampires are merely humans with different eating habits.
We should think that every living organism,
everyone has the right to live.
Humans are ridiculous! PD,
have you asked the polar bears?
Do they think that the humans on this
earth are coexisting with them, too?
Why are they endangered?
They would go nuts!
But to humans, we vampires are just...
an existence no better off than polar bears.
They look just like humans.
Is there no way to distinguish them?
Wait, that means there could be one in our classroom.
Vampire.
Vampire! I will drink all of your blood!
It's tasty!
Ah, stop it!
What's wrong?
I was just kidding.
Watch closely. This is the type of creature we are.
What are you doing?
Can you see this?
Vampires are more superior than humans.
We lost most of our powers not consuming human blood.
We killed our instincts and gave up our powers. What about humans?
What the hell did you do for that coexistence?!
Vampire's unique characteristics...
There's definitely something, but they aren't showing it to us
to protect their small population and their human rights.
Aren't... human rights something that only humans should have?
Vampires...
aren't humans.
Ah...
"Aren't humans."
What is this?
Oh, I don't like it. It smells.
It's a vampire special menu.
They say vampires don't like garlic.
Right, right.
If a vampire appears, I'm going to eat all of that.
I hate it so much.
After the peace treaty, the vampires are having problems.
Anyway...
Yeah, how can that be safe?
How can we coexist? Does that make any sense?
If you want to protect humans a little...
Vampires can't eat this, right?
Do they eat rice with blood?
Blood?
I really don't like that.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's go!
Hi, Ah Ra. This is good, right?
- Yeah...
Is it not? Eat this.
What was that?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
It's okay...
It's okay.
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
Ah, such a waste, this blood.
You should have held it and shot! Are you some kind of goat?
Why are you ripping out the grass and eating it?! Oh, so frustrating. Seriously.
Hey! This...this... Can you not do that?
Even I can do that! Me!
As expected, when it's soccer, it's Chi-Maek.
(Chi-Maek: Chicken and Beer)
Honey!
Song Sun Hwa, my love!
I found a job!
synced by riri13
Really? Indeed my wife is capable.
I found a cafe needing a barista.
What's this smell?
Oh? What smell?
I don't smell anything.
I smell something like chicken.
Did you try to play human again?
Why spend money on something you can't eat?
Is the money rotting?
No...
It's just that next door sells fried chicken.
And we got along well.
Don't even dream of playing soccer.
You couldn't control your strength so we had to move before you were caught.
Now, don't even think about moving.
Let's settle down until Ma Ri graduates, please!
How do humans eat something
so rotten like this?
It'd be a different story if it was chicken blood.
Honey, even if I can't eat it,
if I eat chicken, my heart starts beating.
I must be special.
Joseph, my son! You woke up!
Joseph!
Son! Let's go eat!
Our son! Let's eat.
Ah, you're eating so well. So well.
This batch is tasty.
Right? It's tasty, right?
Ah! It's good.
Anyway, it's Ma Ri's first day, I don't know if she's doing well.
She has to adjust well to her new school.
Our daughter is probably having lunch right now.
Like a normal human, without sticking out,
I have to push through 2 years like I did today.
Baek Ma Ri, you can do well.
Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors! Rock-paper-scissors!
Ha! Dad won. Open your mouth.
It's not the time to change his back teeth, right?
They're still small so there is still a long way.
Honey, did you see the news?
Either way, all the cafes talk about vampires.
I guess it'll take time for it to settle.
Every time this happens, and they persecute us,
it make my heart shiver, Honey.
Aigoo... But this happens every year... Aigoo.
He made a mistake hundreds of times. What is sexual harassment? Sexual harassment!
This time, too, the VCS (Vampire Control System) will most probably issue the "staking" punishment.
Staking?
Breaking news: The notification of the sexual harassment case by the vampire must have been scary.
Around 7:30 this morning, a vampire who harassed a woman at the station
was taken in for investigation by the police.
According to the VCS, the vampire who used his powers in public,
will be faced with "staking."
[Staking; VCS's maximum penalty for the vampire-perpetrator who used his tabooed ability.]
We are still unsure what "staking" is,
but it is understood as a strict punishment for vampires.
There has been no prior victim of sexual harassment by a vampire.
There will be a discussion about the prevention of sexual harassment by a vampire.
Jae Min, this performance is sold out.
You can't buy tickets anymore, but my dad's employee was able to get some.
So what?
Huh? I heard you were in a band in middle school.
They say guitarists dream about seeing this one play.
I want to see it, but I won't go.
Why?
It's just... I quit guitar. If I see it, I'll want to do it again.
You can do it again. You can continue playing then.
Our school doesn't have a band anymore.
Band?
But these tickets will have high competition.
Huh?
Everyone might stand in line because they want to go with you.
Jo Ah Ra, you know you're super popular, right?
I'm curious as to who you will go out with.
Jae Min...
- Then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey...
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Ah, it's so sweet.
Sweet...
What is this good smell?
A flower's scent? No, it's not that.
This smell...
is tasty.
I want to drink some.
Ah, it's so sweet.
Ah, sweet.
Sweet.
Mmm... what is this?
Mmm...
Student! What are you doing?
Sweet.
Did I not put it in my bag?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Why is it so sweet?
A human's blood?
"Congratulations Jae Min, my love, on your 14th birthday."
- Mom
♫ The path where the season passes ♫
♫ Meeting a person like you ♫
♫ Wanting to spend together ♫
I will return to the sky.
♫ time ♫
The day ending the picnic on this beautiful world
says that it was lovely.
The writer is portraying the sky as freedom
and a picnic as the difficult life.
Does anybody remember the dew and sunset from the last class?
♫ Memories come visit ♫
Is there no one?
Class President.
Class President!
- Attention!
It hasn't been 5 minutes since the class has started. Should I stop talking and leave?
I'm sorry.
- Sit.
Hey, he came, he came! What do we do?
Oppa.
Sorry, I'm a little busy right now. Sorry.
Ah, he's so handsome.
- Hey! You saw that, right? "Sorry~"
He touched my hand! No, don't touch my hand!
Don't.
♫ Like I have it, Like I don't have it ♫
♫ Quietly, having it to myself ♫
♫ People you hated ♫
♫ A long time story ♫
♫ Because I couldn't do it all ♫
You need to apologize. I have to receive an apology from you.
♫ Although you may not be interested ♫
Can you hear me now?
- Who are you?
You... don't know me?
Do you know me?
I can't not know. We're in the same class.
I found out for the first time
that someone who can stop my time.
Do you know that?
The world that surrounded me
disappeared for a moment.
In the paused time,
the only sensation,
the feeling of only breathing,
that... was you.
If you have nothing to say, can you move?
- Wait.
The smell of blood! His is sweet, too.
Ah, what do I do? What's wrong with me lately?
What are you doing?
Take some showers.
- Hey...
I shower every day! Do you have mysophobia?
(*Fear of germs.)
Why is someone who has mysophobia attacking only me?
Can you speak so I can understand?
I don't want to.
Let's do it the hard way. I don't want to do it easy.
You need to apologize to me.
For what?
- Look at this.
How can I get a sincere apology from someone who can't even remember?
So, you're saying that you don't know who I am?
You just said, "We're in the same class."
But a girl who transferred 2 days ago
is expected to know everyone's face in class?
I am Jung Jae Min.
So what?
Hey! How much do you not have to care to not know your class president?
And do you think we only saw each other inside the classroom?
Remember, and make sure to apologize to me.
I'm asking you what I did wrong?
Why ask? I told you I was going the hard way. Remember it yourself.
So I'm going to follow you around until you sincerely apologize.
Do you like music?
No.
- Then why are you always carrying this around?
Ear muffs. I don't like noisy things.
Do you know how to play the guitar, by chance?
No.
Then,
what about this?
It looks like guitar chords.
Our son is so handsome.
He grew up so well, right?
Doesn't he look like an European actor?
That's a little too much..
I think they're really cool.
Jae Min does look like that.
You miss him, right?
The bus that will depart at
8:15...
- Time's up.
Please send this well.
I want to give it to him directly, but he won't meet me.
I'll try to convince him.
I feel bad that he even gave up on music, which he loves,
all because of me.
Because he hates me,
he even hates his talent.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
It's fine though.
You... don't know me? You can't even remember me?
"Jung Jae Min, what?"
Baek Ma Ri...
Is this face
that common of a face?
Who are you?
How can you see this face and...
forget it?
You're good looking.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Vampire Lovers @ Viki
Yes?
This...
It looks like they're guitar chords.
It's a habit, right? Lying?
It was a nice piece. Is your dream to be a composer? A musician?
I don't have things like dreams.
Yeah, Mom? I'm on my way. I'm almost there.
I don't have dreams.
Thank you.
Try it. The coffee here is famous, but their orange juice is great too.
Like at home when you squeeze the orange-
I didn't come here to say that I won't.
Then?
I came here to say I definitely won't.
Oh...
Therefore,
stop sending me 20 messages like a stalker, to a student,
Teacher.
At least while drinking the juice-
It's a favor...
Don't say things like how the coffee tastes and how the juice tastes, it gives me goosebumps.
Is it fun to act like that, while we know each other already?
I heard you were basically a legend. The best guitarist in your middle school band.
What kind of legend.
Let's do it! A school band.
Why hide it? I heard you played since you were 5.
Whenever other kids played with toys, you played your guitar.
I heard you held it while sleeping?
Stop it.
Jae Min, let's be honest.
You're dying to play now, right? It was your dream. I heard it from your mom.
I said enough!
Why are you messing with my dream?!
Just be my mom's husband.
Don't try to
cosplay as my new dad.
I don't have those thoughts. It's just regretful.
Just because you rebel, should I throw you away? Your dream?
Ask yourself,
if you have the right
to say something like that.
Don't act like you know me at school.
It would be nice if you could transfer to a different school next semester.
I came here to say that.
It was your birthday a couple days ago.
Accept this.
I can accept it
and throw it away, right?
♫ It is okay. ♫
♫ Please stop it. ♫
♫ You did everything you can. ♫
♫ Don't feel bad alone. ♫
♫  Don't force yourself  ♫
♫ Even though it's lonely ♫
Do you know that?
The one feeling you have
even when time froze.
The feeling that you're only breathing.
That... was you.
♫ Now the one who got hurt the most- will you stop? ♫
♫ Don't try so hard alone. ♫
♫ Don't force yourself ♫
♫ Hiding yourself in the darkness ♫
♫ Only end up as a lonely friend ♫
♫ With the stars and the moon,
tomorrow will probably be better ♫
♫ Try praying in the mirror. ♫