Year after year, always trying
to improve, improve.
With more experience,
with more objectives, more desires,
proving to my family,
proving to my dad,
that the decisions I took
in the beginning, at the age of 12,
were the best ones.
There are people who love me.
There are people who hate me...
who say that I'm arrogant,
that I'm vain or I'm this and that.
That's part of my success.
I was made to be the best.
My dear boy!
Your mother's heart almost exploded.
That's what I wanted to say
to you too, Ronaldo!
Oh, my dear boy, you deserved it!
The Ballon d'Or is the very best
individual award for any player.
It means you're considered
the best player in the world.
To see Messi win the Ballon d'Or
four times in a row
was difficult for me.
After he won the second or third
in a row, I said,
"I'm not coming here anymore."
Why do I come here
if I am doing so well for my team?
Why should I come here?
I have to win more Ballons d'Or.
For me, the year gone by
was the best year of my career.
Without any doubt.
I try to fight with my
weapons every day, every match,
throughout my career,
to be the best ever.
That second Ballon d'Or
was obviously one of the most
beautiful moments in my life.
But my ambition ends up
always wanting more,
always wanting more.
A new year,
goals to score, trophies to win...
That is the way I live my life.
- Good morning.
Good morning, Cris.
Come here!
- Give Daddy a kiss!
- Yes. OK.
Silly head.
Let's go.
- Done!
- Give me five! Well done.
The Champions League final
is almost here
and Carlo Ancelotti's Real Madrid
is searching for a new title.
For the whites, it could be La Decima.
The last time that Real Madrid
won the trophy was in 2002.
...for sure,
Cristiano is doing very well.
Clearly, Ronaldo is on top form,
clearly ready to win.
I knew that after Real Madrid hired me,
the pressure would mount.
Real Madrid wanted to win
the Champions League, La Decima,
and obviously, to win,
you need to have the best players.
- Whoops!
- I didn't get hurt.
Come.
Shall we race to the door?
- Yes.
- Now!
I'm going to win!
I won! I won! See?
I was at Manchester for six years.
And... I won practically everything
there was to win.
- Impressive, isn't it?
- This is incredible.
- Is there going to be a match or not?
- No.
That was when Real Madrid showed up.
They were willing to pay
a lot of money for me.
I wanted more. I wanted another league.
I wanted a different kind of football,
and I wanted a different chapter,
a different challenge in my life.
The stadium was full
to welcome me to the team.
90,000 people at the stadium.
I felt like a star,
like a pop star or a Hollywood star.
Today the time has arrived.
Today we welcome to his new home,
today we welcome Cristiano Ronaldo.
For me, I've achieved
my childhood dream,
which was to play for Real Madrid.
I didn't expect the stadium
to be so full today just to see me.
I can't believe it.
Incredible!
Let's go.
One, two, three.
Hala Madrid!
If I had to choose one title,
the Champions League
would surely be the most important.
The mythical Decima
was the most wanted trophy in Madrid.
Preparing the shot.
That one might be a goal.
Goal! Goal for Atlético Madrid.
It's clearly in.
Godin scored. Minute 36.
Atlético takes the lead
on the scoreboard.
400 million viewers all over the world
in more than 200 countries
are watching this match.
And now, Real Madrid
needs to improve and recover
if they want to win La Decima.
And the world's best player,
as well as Real Madrid's,
17 goals in this
year's Champions League...
He is a true champion.
Nothing is impossible for him.
Cristiano.
As we did the first time,
we're all going to shout together.
One, two, three. "Hala Madrid."
One, two, three...
Hala Madrid!
He's a very big man, isn't he?
Bigger than you.
No. Bigger in size,
but Daddy is stronger.
Didn't you know that?
Look. Where's your schoolbag?
Look. Which car is missing?
The Ro...
No, the Rover is outside.
Which car is missing here?
Look at them all. Go on.
Which one is missing?
The Porsche?
Look properly! Look properly!
- The Royce.
- No.
One that is very fast, very fast.
Lamborghini.
- Ah! You didn't know.
- And where is it?
It went to change a tire.
A tire blew up.
Go! Go! Go!
I'm going to be a goalkeeper.
OK, Dad?
- No, I don't want that.
- But I do.
A goalkeeper?
Are you joking or what?
Go! Go!
Great defense!
Dad, I'm going to teach you
how to shoot a penalty.
To shoot a penalty,
you place the ball here.
But don't go too far away
because otherwise you won't score.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
You have to shoot hard like this
so that you score.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, but...
- Will you teach me how to do it later?
- Yes. When you're a player...
- What?
- You'll see when we play football.
- Are you going to teach me?
- Yes.
Football has always been my passion.
It was always
what I enjoyed doing the most.
I was born on the island of Madeira;
more specifically in the
neighborhood of Quinta Falcão.
I wanted to be someone in football.
I started playing football at Andorinha.
At the time, my father
was Andorinha's kit man.
I stayed at Andorinha for a couple
of years. Then I went to Nacional.
It was one of the best teams in Madeira.
And then I went to Sporting,
leaving Madeira at the age of 12
and going to Lisbon,
a different city, the capital.
I remember leaving home.
My siblings were crying, my mother...
Even my father
was more emotional that day.
But they knew that it was
an opportunity I wanted in life.
At Sporting, we were happy
to find a new family.
There were many footballers
with plenty of talent.
But Cristiano had something special.
He did different things.
He was never satisfied
with the amount he did.
He always wanted more.
It's the most expensive transfer ever
for a kid his age,
around 15 million euros.
On Manchester's website,
they say 17.3 million.
I don't understand why it's different.
Probably it went to his manager.
It's one more victory
for manager Jorge Mendes.
This was Jorge Mendes's big season.
Tiago, it's Jorge Mendes
from Gestifute speaking. Good evening.
I'm in Madrid.
We have to meet up.
One of these days
we'll go out for lunch.
Jorge Mendes is one of
the most important businessmen
in Portuguese football.
He represents big names like
Cristiano Ronaldo and José Mourinho.
Jorge Mendes is a super-agent, with
a group of footballers and coaches
worth more than 650 million euros.
The businessman does business
with all the big names in Europe
and represents Mourinho,
Ronaldo, Nani
as well as many other names from
Portuguese and international football.
OK, very good. Very good.
I met Jorge when I was 16...
...and that's when practically
everything began.
I felt a great empathy with him
right from the very first moment.
Right to this day, everything Jorge
said would happen has happened.
Little Jorge. Dance!
Hold on! Come here.
Shall we go home?
Let's go home.
Straighten his feet.
- Put him in the back.
- C'mon, son, go in the back.
- Open it.
- It's open.
- See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow, Mum.
I have limpets at home for you.
I'll tell Henrique
to come and get them.
- OK, and can he cook them?
- I'll tell him to cook them.
You need to explain to him how to do it.
Hi, how are you?
- Fine. You?
- Fine.
Hi, how are you?
Fine, and you?
Look, Daddy's going to make a drink.
Do you want to try a little bit?
- No.
- No? OK. Then I'll do it just for me.
Alright?
Or do you not want a little bit?
- Just a little bit.
- A little bit for me.
Just a little bit for you to try.
Yes. I want the Portug... No...
- The Ferrari one?
- Yes, because it's mine.
The Ferrari one.
See if you like it.
That's for you to become very strong!
Look at Daddy's arm, look.
Don't you want to be big like Daddy?
Huh?
Oh, wow!
It's very good.
Come on. Finish painting
so we can go and play football.
Come on.
It's nearly done.
You like it, huh?
Good.
You will be... Whoa!
- You're going to be very strong!
- Touch it.
That's it. Look at the ball.
I tricked you.
That's it.
Now it's bedtime.
Come. This way.
To your bed!
Give Daddy a kiss.
Sleep well. Give Daddy a hug.
Come on. Let's go.
Wait! Let me take out the blankets.
Go.
Bye. See you later.
There are twelve days remaining until
Portugal's first game at the World Cup
and the main concern
for the Portuguese football team
is the most famous acronym
in the world... CR7.
Cristiano Ronaldo
has a physical problem.
He is limited by injuries
to his thigh and knee.
Portugal's going to win the World Cup!
Before the Champions League,
with 15 days to go, I was injured.
I think it was an accumulation.
Every year I play more than 60 games.
Either you stop for two or three months
or you learn to live with the pain
and have the psychological strength
to endure it.
I can endure the pain because I think
there's something stronger.
Maybe if I didn't feel the pain,
maybe I wouldn't be as good as I am.
Give us a smile! Give us a smile!
Hello?
Are you joking or what?
Yes?
- Hello?
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Yes, Mum.
- You don't have any network, Ronaldo.
- Mum, I'm inside the hotel.
You don't want me to go out to
the woods to find a network, do you?
OK. OK. Call me when you have signal.
Will do. OK.
- Here, Ronaldo. Talk to your father!
- Hello, Daddy!
- Send kisses.
- Kisses.
- Say "Go, Portugal!"
- Go, Portugal!
I love you very much.
Daddy loves you very much too, son.
Kisses.
- Kisses.
- Bye.
Cristiano, are you
feeling 100 percent now?
99.9 percent.
OK. This part's cool.
And...
It's Cristiano's favorite color.
I love you, Daddy.
When are you coming back?
It's now. It's now.
Beautiful! A round of applause.
Beautiful!
Wherever the national team goes,
all the attention
is on Cristiano Ronaldo.
Naturally, we're talking
about the best player in the world.
Cristiano Ronaldo says he feels
99.9 percent ready for the World Cup.
CR7 left for Campinas in a good mood.
Cristiano Ronaldo
shows that he's confident.
He's not afraid of using the leg
that's fragile at the moment.
We need to remember
it's patella tendonitis...
Gaspar. Gaspar.
Did you bring the ice?
Gaspar, I'm talking to you.
Why are you asking now we're on the bus
rather than outside?
He forgot about you yesterday
and forgot about me today.
Honestly, Gaspar!
If it had been Cristiano asking,
he'd bring a suitcase full of ice.
A suitcase!
There couldn't be more at stake
for Ronaldo and the Portuguese team.
It's going to be essential for Ronaldo
to do well in this World Cup
if he's to retain his Ballon d'Or.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
- The ball, the ball... Ball.
- Ball.
Let's crush them!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Let's go!
Let's believe we are a great team.
No. He has the telephone number
of the agent.
Don't worry! He will take
care of everything.
The match is going to start
in half an hour.
Any other player would not have
played in the World Cup
because Cristiano was in
no condition to play a World Cup.
Everybody that I spoke to said,
"He's going to put his career at risk."
"He shouldn't play."
It could have become a serious problem.
It's over. It's over.
Look here! It's time to wake up.
Frustration starts kicking in
on the pitch.
That's what happened.
Frustration, being beaten four-nil,
starting the World Cup
in the worst possible way.
It was the worst thing
that could have happened to us.
We hadn't met people's expectations,
what the Brazilian people
helped us with.
I think we couldn't
give it back to them.
Look at that. Look!
He reacted quickly.
Let her go, man! Let her go!
Let her go!
She was at the hotel waiting
for you yesterday.
- This girl?
- Yes, the same one.
- I didn't see her.
- Cristiano, she jumped this fence.
Yes, security told me.
We'll meet her in a bit.
She's fine physically.
She must be physically fit
to be able to jump this fence.
- And you? Are you physically fit?
- Everything's fine.
- Everything? A hundred percent?
- A hundred percent.
Thanks, Cristiano Ronaldo.
Don't they want to talk to me as well?
Thank you for everything.
I did it!
- You did?
- I did.
- What did Cristiano tell you?
- He knows I exist.
He asked me to stay calm
and stop crying, to take care.
He asked what my name is
and I asked him to follow me on Twitter.
- Three times a day...
- Don't exceed three per day.
- Can I take one now?
- Yes, you can.
- At night?
- Exactly.
OK. And tomorrow?
If you want to, take it when
you're feeling too anxious like now.
I'm going to take one now because
I'm already feeling agitated. OK.
- OK?
- OK.
- Hello?
- What's up, Maria? How's everything?
Have you taken the sedatives?
- Have you taken the sedatives?
- What?
Have you taken the sedatives?
Take it easy. It's only a game.
Don't be upset, and don't stress out
because it'll go well.
It'll go well, God willing.
Take it easy! Don't be upset!
It's only a game...
It's only a football game,
not a matter of life and death.
- No one's going to die!
- OK, but... We have to win!
OK. But take it easy. No worries.
No worries. No worries.
OK, then. A kiss, Mum. Bye. Bye.
Carla?
My young man is looking beautiful,
isn't he?
- Both of them!
- Ha! No, the little one.
I'm talking about the little one.
And so, tomorrow... Are you ready
to watch the World Cup game?
I am, but it's always that thing
and it's a match we have to win.
- Of course.
- We have to win.
And you see, being old,
I get more nervous.
- No, you're not...
- It's true. It's true.
I think that when I was younger,
I dealt with it better,
whether they won or lost.
But not now. I suffer more now.
But, Dolores, you must be used to
watching your son's matches by now.
Yes, but when it comes
to special matches, it's different.
This is the second game for Portugal
in the group stage facing the USA.
They need to win after their awful
performance against Germany.
She lives my world as well.
She lives my joy. She lives my sadness.
It's as if she plays football
and not me.
I often say there are times
when my mother looks older
because of football.
Goal!
Portugal! Portugal!
Portugal!
It's quite complicated for a mother
to watch a son who needs to win.
I get sad.
I get worried.
And I suffer a lot.
When he gets hit,
it's like they hit me as well.
Because I've always
liked football a lot,
I wanted to have a son
who'd be a great player.
But I never thought in my life
that I'd have a son
who'd be a professional player
and be the best in the world.
Go! Go! Go! Goal!
Dinis, be quiet!
Go! Go! Go!
Now's the time. Score now, Ronaldo!
No. I'm going outside.
No. No. No.
- Pass me my flip-flops.
- But it's not... It's over now!
OK. But pass me my flip-flops!
I'm going on my own.
I'm going for a walk.
Oh, Ronaldo! Damn it!
I risked sending my son to Lisbon
when he was 12 years old
which wasn't easy at all.
I felt like I was abandoning him,
but it was for a good reason.
Because I worked hard
to raise four children.
But he was an unwanted child,
but that son gave me so much joy.
All that I have I owe to that son.
However many people turn up, you'll
always be well received, won't you?
Is that taxi over there available?
- A photo with you, please?
- The first one, yeah?
We had arrived in Portugal.
I didn't say anything to anyone,
got in a taxi and went to the hotel
because the next day I wanted to leave.
I wanted to go away on holiday.
I didn't even want to go to Portugal.
I didn't want to come to Spain.
I wanted to travel.
I wanted to go anywhere else
where I wouldn't follow it,
because I was sad.
I have no doubt that
the World Cup made my injury worse.
I feel sad.
I feel that things are not flowing.
I don't feel any improvement
in my injury.
I could have recovered by now.
If I could go back,
I wouldn't have gone to the World Cup.
Are you playing?
- It's looking hard, isn't it?
- It's you.
You're well trained.
I'm seeing if I'm lucky enough
to be able to pay you the 40 euros.
What do you mean?
You're almost like
Cristiano "King" Ronaldo.
Nah, not yet.
There's still a long way to go.
But it's getting better.
So you're pleased! Come on. Sit here.
I have to watch it, don't I?
It's only us two, right?
What's the suit?
- Spades, spades, spades.
- No, no.
Which one was it?
It's spades! Watch out for the game
or you'll lose.
Five, six, seven,
eight...
- Three...
- Four, five, six, seven.
That's it.
Ten! One, two,
three, four, five...
Seven, eight, nine, ten.
That's it. Get off.
Look. It's a draw, the game.
We both won.
We'll do the rest this afternoon,
alright?
Give me a snuggle and a kiss.
Give me a hug, my darling.
I consider myself to be
an isolated person.
I know what's best for me.
And the best for me is
I come home,
completely disconnect from the world,
media, television, football
because I know that the next day I'll be
pulled back into that world again.
I like to be quiet.
I like not feeling pressure
after training, after the games.
I like to enter my world.
I am at home.
I'm with the people I like.
I'm with my son.
And I am at peace with myself.
I have everything.
There's nothing that I don't have.
But people are always waiting
for me to make a mistake,
to accuse me, to criticize me.
It's difficult. It's very difficult.
Wait. Wait. I can see him.
I can see him.
I think I will always be observed
in a different way.
But that's part of what I have
achieved in the world of football.
Maybe when I end my career,
things will become quieter.
What name have you chosen
for this baby?
Hugo Tomas.
Are you aware that you are
obliged to educate him in the faith
so this child can keep
God's commandments?
Yes.
And you, the godparents, are you willing
to help his parents in this task?
Yes.
Hugo Tomas, the Christian community
receives you with great joy.
I do the Cross on you as a sign
of Christ the Savior.
The celebration has concluded.
Congratulations on the new Christian
in your home.
And one last thing, later, outside,
if you don't mind,
take a selfie with me. OK?
Have a picture together. Go.
Cristiano Ronaldo has lost his father.
Dinis Aveiro leaves our world
at the age of 53.
His condition deteriorated
in the month of July.
Cristiano Ronaldo booked an air
ambulance to take his dad to London,
but his kidneys and liver
couldn't hold out any longer.
Ronaldo's father drank a lot.
He had cirrhosis
and he died due to drinking.
Ronaldo did everything
he could to save his father,
but he couldn't.
I think it was because he joined
the Portuguese Colonial War in Angola
and he returned angry
because of the war.
And when he came back,
he felt very angry
and although he never mistreated
his children, he never did,
I became his victim.
My father, he was very funny
when he was drunk.
He used to tell a lot of stories.
He used to sing.
He was funny.
He was drunk nearly every day.
And when that happens,
it's not easy to have a conversation
to get to know my father a bit more.
I'm not ashamed to say it.
I didn't really get to know
my father for real, from the heart,
to open up and tell him things.
I never had those kinds of
conversations with him.
If you ask me why my father
became an alcoholic, I don't know.
Maybe he was frustrated with life.
I don't know.
I don't know and I don't care.
I feel some frustration
because obviously I wanted
a different father,
a dad who could be more present
to see my achievements.
That's what frustrates me the most.
The fact that he can't see
all my successes as a player,
as a person, as a father as well.
But I think that I managed
to handle things in his absence.
Give me five!
Ah! You tricked me.
Cristiano Ronaldo
has become the father of a boy.
The news was announced by the footballer
himself on Facebook and Twitter.
The Portuguese international
doesn't reveal the mother's name
and says he'll have
sole custody of the child.
Ronaldo announced the birth of his son
first in English and then in Portuguese
so there were no remaining doubts.
But as for the mother's identity,
not a word.
Irina Shayk is Cristiano Ronaldo's
current girlfriend,
but everything suggests that the son
is from a previous relationship.
For two hours the reporters waited
for a glimpse of the idol and his son.
It was only CR7, who left his house
to say that he was happy
but upset at the same time.
I'm happy, but you disappoint me.
You're always here disturbing me.
Always walking around the house.
And you make me upset by doing this.
Regarding the mystery surrounding
little CR's mother, not a single word.
Are you going to announce
anything else about the child?
What do you mean?
The big question we all have basically
is if the child was...
That's pointless. That's pointless.
It's pointless to ask because...
Was it done at a clinic?
Don't go there. It's pointless.
I've said everything I have to say.
I'd like you to give me some privacy.
You can color it here, here, here...
- OK?
- OK.
I always had this dream
of having a son
to be my successor.
I wanted to be a young father,
and I was.
I was 25.
Because I wanted to be able
to follow him
during his development
as a person, as a man.
That was always a dream of mine.
Obviously, Cristiano has been
a big influence on me.
I have learnt to be calmer,
more cautious.
I have learnt a lot
about being a father.
People speculate that it was
with this girl or the other,
or a surrogate mother.
I've never told anyone and never will.
I think I should keep that to myself.
And later, when Cristiano is grown up,
then I will talk to him
and tell him what I did, what I felt,
everything that went through my mind.
Some kids never get to know
their parents,
neither father nor mother.
Having a father is good enough.
I don't care what other people say.
It doesn't bother me.
I always thought, and still think,
that he will understand me.
I can't believe it!
He doesn't have anybody
apart from his father and me,
and so he does spend
a lot of time with me.
Now how is he going to score?
Pass! Pass it forward!
I'm not bothered
about who the mother is.
I just want to give my grandson love
and educate him as Ronaldo asked me to,
as I did for him.
He reminds me of Ronaldo
when he was a child
and I see little Cristiano
just like his dad.
Goal!
Daddy!
Great!
Look, it was Daddy!
Cristiano shoots and... Goal!
The winner of the Ballon d'Or!
- The best player of last season!
- Goal! Goal! Goal!
Goal! Goal! Goal!
Cristiano scores
his 11th goal of the season.
The goal record of Cristiano Ronaldo
is astonishing,
even surpassing the total
number of goals
scored by some teams
in the Spanish league.
Hat trick for Cristiano Ronaldo.
It's his 13th goal in the league
in only seven matches.
You have to show yourself
that you really are good.
That's always my priority,
to prove to myself
that I still have the ability,
that I can do better things,
wanting to win more than other people,
demonstrating
that I'm better than others.
Your son says that you're going
to score two goals.
One for me and one for him.
- Yes, yes. A dream.
- Yes. He said that to me.
We'll win five-nil.
God willing.
Yes. Goodbye.
Speak soon. Kisses. Speak soon.
Bye. Bye. Bye.
The Ballon d'Or is obvious.
I don't need to ask your opinion.
But you'll be there on January 12th.
Are you expecting an emotional reaction
from Cristiano Ronaldo if he wins?
I can only tell you I don't know
what is going to happen.
The only thing I can tell you
is that there has never been
a year like this one.
The difference between first and second
is so big that there is no doubt.
And if Cristiano doesn't win,
it would be best that
they stopped doing this event,
that it didn't appear any longer
in the history of this trophy.
Because the difference, truly,
is so great,
because it's not even worth
anyone asking,
"Will it be A, B or C?"
The difference is so great
that in the history of this trophy,
there has never been so great
a difference as this year, 2014.
The difference was an abyss,
and so there can only be one winner.
Well, that's OK. I'll organize it.
You're going crazy!
No, no. I was talking to someone here.
With the father of a footballer
who's going to be phenomenal.
OK.
It's an extra motivation
that he prods me all the time
and always roots for me,
believing that I can always do better,
believing that I can always
be even better.
His desire to show the world
that I'm the best ever
is a reason for happiness.
He became an older brother.
He became a father.
Jorge is another member of my family.
I'm the brother
of the best footballer in the world
and so I don't need anyone
to notice me. I don't need that.
My father taught me
it's better to keep silent.
My father used to say,
"A silent person wins more."
If I applied myself and trained,
I'm sure I'd also be a footballer.
I'm absolutely sure of it.
I had some talent.
Ronaldo could have gone down
the wrong path.
But he took the right path, and I was
happy that he chose that path,
working to become a footballer.
I've had issues with addiction.
I was already drinking
at the age of 20.
I worked for a long time with my father.
I worked in construction.
30 years ago,
everyone working in construction
would drink alcohol. Everyone.
I asked for help.
Then I had a relapse again.
Then, on my own,
I told myself it was enough
if I wanted to have a decent life
and if I didn't want to die young.
I stopped, and until today,
my life's healthy. Thank God.
From the day I pulled myself together,
Ronaldo has always helped me.
We have to get away from people
who are always in trouble.
Addictions, drugs and alcohol
won't get us anywhere.
He knows that he made mistakes.
He made some mistakes in life,
and he's the first to admit that
and these are moments
he managed to overcome.
And so for me today, he's someone
that I trust with my projects.
He owns my museum.
He's my right arm in many things.
He's someone I will trust
for the rest of my days
and he's a businessman.
Like they say, if we won't help
our family, who will we help?
He might have gone through a bad period,
but God gave him a new start
which was having a perfect family.
Thank you, brother, for all you've done.
I can't. I can't. I can't now.
OK. OK.
Look! Do you know something?
Do you have any idea
what day it is today?
Forget that! Call me after the game!
Call me after the game!
Hello.
Will you give your godfather a kiss?
Who will win?
- Who will win?
- Madrid!
- Real Madrid.
How many goals will Daddy score?
Two? No, Four! Two is not enough.
Four, four, four.
At least four.
I'm afraid of the other guy.
He's the only one
who can win the Ballon d'Or. Huh?
- The other guy could destroy everything.
- No. No, he won't.
I think rivalry
is always created by the press.
The relationship with Messi,
in the last year, was much better.
We've spoken more about ourselves.
He asked me about my injury,
how my old injury was
from the World Cup,
asking about the family...
I looked at him not as a rival
but as a person
who makes me a better player
and I make him a better player.
We are always busting our balls
to see who's better.
Penalty! Penalty! Penalty! Penalty!
Penalty!
Cristiano Ronaldo is at the ball.
This is a spot
he hardly ever misses from.
Cristiano shoots and goal!
An equalizer in El Clásico.
16 goals for Cristiano in La Liga,
and the fifth penalty
for the Portuguese player.
They appear to be
on the best form ever.
Ronaldo and Real Madrid
are clearly imposing themselves
in this match against Barcelona.
Goal, Cristiano.
The three points stay with Madrid
at the Bernabéu.
Real Madrid and the fans celebrate
this very important victory
for Carlo Ancelotti's team.
A three-one win.
The local team, Real Madrid,
was undoubtedly better than Barcelona.
It's a huge party here
at the Santiago Bernabéu.
The people I trust the most
and that I feel the most...
Esteem. Esteem.
- Esteem and friendship for.
- And feel friendship for.
If you want to talk, you can do it!
But in fact the people I trust
the most are present here.
I want that to be clear. It's true.
I'm saying it from the heart.
I hope we can do this again
because it'll mean we're happy
and things are...
- And alive.
- Alive and doing well. Thank you, all.
Well done!
- To the best!
- Health!
The best thing to do
is put all your money
in that vault you have in your room.
It doesn't fit.
Do you think it fits in there?
Big Jorge!
We started from nothing.
Jorge, we started from nothing
and now...
Big Jorge didn't have anything either.
He went around selling videotapes and...
- And playing music.
- And look at the man now.
Straw hats.
- And now he's always wearing Rolex.
- This one's a fake.
I come from a good family.
They were just dirt poor.
They were.
- Old times!
- Great episodes.
Great episodes lived with big Jorge.
Now for the best one, Jorge.
You need a drink.
As for my friend Hugo,
I still remember the past and things
that don't need to be talked about now.
I'm proud of him because he
overcame his adversities.
To think back then,
that we'd be here today,
and you've got businesses in your hands
and ambitions for a bright future
for you and your family.
I'll give you a kiss.
Now, after the mother I had,
you're the mother I'd like to have had.
This is... This is...
My special son.
I don't need many words,
because he knows it.
I live obsessed about him every day.
But he deserves it.
It's not because...
You could not be everything you are.
But I'll tell you something,
I fight for you every day.
I feel very proud to be able
to fight for you every day.
I want to do it with conviction.
You deserve it.
You're a lot more
than I could ever do for you!
It's nothing.
In terms of your value,
I could do twice what I do.
It'll never be enough
to be up to your level,
your quality,
both human and sporting qualities.
You're a monster!
This is the best in the world,
the best footballer in the world.
The best sportsman, I tell you.
And I mean it.
There's really no doubt about it.
He's the best in the world and everyone
will recognize that for sure.
All the world. No one will be
indifferent to that.
He's the best sportsman
in the world ever
and I'm proud to be standing
next to a guy like this
because it's a truly impressive thing!
Oscar! Give him an Oscar!
If I didn't know you,
I'd ask you for an autograph.
- Jorge...
- You lost your glass somewhere.
A toast to Jorge!
Jorge is the best.
Jorge. Top!
Top, top, top.
The Ballon d'Or is a day
when your heart beats faster.
You sweat more. You're more anxious,
more tired, both psychologically
and physically.
It's a very intense day.
My mother, my siblings,
I feel they were also very nervous.
Even Jorge Mendes.
Everyone who was with me.
It stays for life.
People who like me,
the family, the fans,
they never forget about it
because it's the climax
of a year's work,
of a career that started
when I was 11 years old,
playing football always
with the goal of being the best,
winning trophies, winning titles,
having a good life, making money...
Everything. It's all part
of the same package.
It's a card inside an envelope
that can change so much.
You're a chicken.
My son accompanying his dad
and seeing with his own eyes
the glories of his father,
that's unique.
He's already proud of me.
He shows off my trophies.
That makes me an even happier person.
You're a clown!
I'm the same as you.
Let me see if your hands are cold.
You're cold.
I just had a shower
to wash bad luck away from my body.
- To wash what?
- Bad luck.
Come here. Take a photo
with me and Ronaldo, please.
You need to be very well behaved
otherwise Daddy won't buy you
anything tomorrow.
Otherwise Daddy won't win.
I always do. And will you cry?
I will.
I'm always the first one to cry.
- Why are they shouting?
- Because of the players.
What did they call you
when you went outside?
Who's that guy there?
Who's that guy over there?
The one wearing a suit. Who is it?
Go on. Go on.
Are you OK? Yes?
High-five him.
What's up? Are you well?
Are you being shy now?
He's shy now.
Who's that?
He's being shy now.
- Look at that shyness!
- He can't believe it's him!
- It's Messi.
- Give Daddy a kiss.
A kiss? Why?
I'm always giving you kisses.
He can't believe it.
And why do you like playing football?
Bye. Bye.
Done.
You'll see that I'll end up
without any teeth.
Come here.
Nearly there, nearly there...
Wait!
You see?
Everything's possible.
"And he was crazy for her!"
Done!
You're the best, man! The best!
He was a child
that I wanted to abort.
God didn't want that to happen,
and I was blessed because of that,
and God did not punish me.
Sometimes Ronaldo makes fun of me
and says,
"You didn't want me to be born."
"But now you see
that I'm here helping all of you."
And, well, sometimes,
we have a laugh about that.
It's like a family relationship.
And after that, I'm passionate
about his game,
about the way he plays,
the way he dedicates himself.
I see Cristiano like a son,
like a real son.
I've lived life's sorrows,
so did Ronaldo,
and life took a turn.
It's been a journey.
Life can really turn around.
The world is round.
He's our protector
and he always helped us
and everything we have today
we owe to him.
He's going through
a great moment of fame.
He is, these days.
I'm enjoying it greatly.
- How does a father feel?
- He's really standing out.
The father likes it.
It's always good. I feel emotional.